bookeo.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy – Bookeo

**Effective date: August 11, 2017**

Bookeo Pty Ltd (referred to here as “Bookeo”, “Our”, “us”, “we”) provides its Service (as defined below) to you through its web site located at bookeo.com and any of the internet subdomains of bookeo.com (the “Site”). The “Service” includes (a) the Site, (b) the system, tools and services provided by Bookeo through the Site, and (c) all software, data, text, images, sounds, video, and content made available through the Site or Service (collectively referred to as the “Content”). Any new features added to or augmenting the Service are also subject to this Privacy Policy.

By using the service and / or accessing the Site, you agree to the Privacy Policy which is set out in this document. The Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your conduct on the Site and /or through your use of the Service.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

In this Privacy Policy, we use the following terms to describe different types of visitors to the Site. Our customers are called “Businesses” and our Businesses’ customers are called “Customers”. We use the word “staff” to describe persons to whom Businesses give a user account to access the Business data on the Site. These people are collectively described in this Privacy Policy as “Users” of the Site.

This Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms of service applicable to the Site. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the Site.

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to the Site, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual (“personal information”). This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the Site, will be dealt with. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. This Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome your comments and feedback.

### 1\. Personal Information

Personal information about Users to the Site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries to third parties. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.

### 2\. Use of Information

Personal information that Users submit to the Site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted or for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose, unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection.

For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products and services, enhancing, improving or modifying our products and services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities.

### 3\. Personal information that we collect about Businesses and staff

We collect personal information about Businesses and their staff in order for Businesses to take full advantage of the Service. This includes but is not limited to staff names, email addresses, business address, telephone numbers and availability. You may access this information at any time by logging in to your account.

We may also collect credit card details and billing address in order to process payments for the use of the Service. These credit card details are securely transmitted to a selected third party (payment gateway) for the sole purpose of processing such payments. The payment gateway is responsible for securely storing such credit card details and for limiting their access to authorized users.

We do not store credit card details in our Site or in any facility operated by us. We may, however, store partial credit card details (card type, expiry date, and no more than 3 digits from the card number), in order to let the Business identify and update the credit card details used for payment processing.

### 4\. Personal information that we collect about Customers

We collect personal information about Customers in order for Customers to take full advantage of the service. This information includes but is not limited to names, email addresses, addresses, telephone numbers, dates of birth, and other personal information as required by the Business that the Customer intends to do business with. This personal information will be transferred to the intended Business and its staff.

We may also collect credit card details and billing address on behalf of the Business. These credit card details are securely transmitted to a selected third party (payment gateway) for the sole purpose of processing payments on behalf of the Business. The credit card details of a Customer are never shown in full to a Business or its staff. The payment gateway is responsible for securely storing such credit card details and for limiting their access to authorized users.

We do not store credit card details in our Site or in any facility operated by us. We may, however, store partial credit card details (card type, expiry date, and no more than 3 digits from the card number), in order to let the Customer identify and update the credit card details used for payment processing.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Bookeo Pty Ltd send an email containing the text that is input by the friend. The email address is not stored or used for any other purposes.  
Your friend may contact us at [privacy@bookeo.com](mailto:privacy@bookeo.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### 5\. Disclosure to third parties

Personal User information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, please contact us at [privacy@bookeo.com](mailto:privacy@bookeo.com)

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as our payment process or analytics provider. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

In certain situations, Bookeo Pty Ltd may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

If Bookeo is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### 6\. Security

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.

For your safety and protection, we never store credit card numbers on our servers. Where necessary, credit card numbers are stored by our payment gateway provider (“Eway”), or by one of the payment gateways preselected by us and chosen by our Businesses with the use of encryption during transmission. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### 7\. Email addresses

We may send notification emails to the email address provided by Users regarding bookings, cancellations, purchases, membership subscriptions, billing or other activities that are part of the Service and that are related to the User.

We may send periodic company news, updates, and/or related product or service information. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or accessing the email preferences in your account settings page.

Businesses may send marketing emails to their Customers at their discretion. If Businesses send marketing emails through the Service, Customers can always opt-out an any time by simply clicking on the link provided at the bottom of the email.

### 8\. Log files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you.

### 9\. Tracking Technologies

We Bookeo Pty Ltd and our partners use technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

**Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting** – We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://preferences.truste.com/) . Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### 10\. Access to Information

We will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. Upon request Bookeo Pty Ltd will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by emailing our Privacy Team at privacy@bookeo.com. In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to exercise your rights under GDPR, and request and access any personal data we have collected about you, please [click here](https://www.bookeo.com/contact/dsr/) or send an email to privacy@bookeo.com

### 11\. Links to other sites

We provide links to Web sites outside of our web sites, as well as to third party Web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that Web site and its privacy policy.

Our web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums.

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@bookeo.com](mailto:privacy@bookeo.com).

### 12\. Problems or questions

If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our online [booking system](https://bookeo.com/), we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us. For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner’s web site: <https://www.oaic.gov.au/>.

Bookeo Pty Ltd  
18/30 Denison Street  
Bondi Junction NSW 2022  
Australia

Privacy Team E-mail: privacy@bookeo.com

Data Protection Officer E-mail: dpo@bookeo.com

* * *

EU Representative Art. 27 GDPR

Rickert Rechtsanwaltsgesellschaft mbH  
Kaiserplatz 7-9  
53225 Bonn  
Germany  
datenschutz@rickert.net
